听着  我听高层的线人说
Listen, I heard from a connect in the Ivory Tower.
有传言称
And there's rumors flying around
他们在召集大陪审团
about they're convening a grand jury.
我不会让你承担这一切  老埃
I'm not letting you take the heat for this, Al.
如果继续这么下去  我就去自首
It keeps going, I'm turning myself in.
听着  我知道会有这么一天
Look, I knew what I was getting into...
帮助艾琳转移尸体是我的决定
helping Erin move that body, that was my call.
那不是一切的开端  这都怪我
That's not where it started. It's on me.
安东尼奥打入了拉丁少年帮
Oh, Antonio. Infiltrated the Latin Players.
他要和一个叫佩雷斯的人做买卖
He's about to do a buy with a guy named Perez.
是从得州运来的液体冰毒
Liquid meth shipment arriving from Texas.
霍斯特德  你在哪里
Halstead, what's your position?
100码外  我们听着呢
100 yards out, and we have audio.
-阿特沃特  -收到
- Atwater? - 10-4.
我们时刻盯着
We got ears and an anchor down.
等得州来的车一到
Once the truck from Texas arrives,
等安东尼奥发信号就行动
wait for Antonio's signal, then we move in.
来了
There you go.
-喂  -还有十分钟到
- Sí? - Diez minutos de distancia.
-你在哪里  -南边入口
- Where are you? - Near the south entrance
附近...下车
of the...whoa! Out of the van!
怎么回事
Whoa, what the hell was that?
赶紧去南入口
Move toward the south entrance now.
去那边看看怎么回事
Let's get over there and see what's going on.
不行  你也听到枪声了
No way, ese. You heard those gunshots.
有人倒地  老大  但没看到车
We got one down here, boss, but no van.
继续找
Keep going.
他是刚刚
Hey, he's the cat
安东尼奥的人联系的喽啰
that Antonio's guy was just talking to.
这是佩雷斯的号码
It's Perez's number.
他本来就在运液体冰毒的车上
All right, so he's in the car with the liquid meth.
他叫伊曼纽·加西亚  驾驶证是墨西哥的
It's Emmanuel Garcia. It's a Mexican license.
伙计们  这里有新鲜的血迹
Guys, we got fresh blood over here.
鲁塞克  你和我们一起
All right, Ruz, you're with us.
-凯文  待在尸体边  -好的
- Kev, stay with the body. - Got it.
芝加哥警局  不许动
Chicago PD! Don't move!
我动不了
I can't.
谁打中你的
Who shot you, huh?
5021G  紧急情况  有人受伤
5021 George, emergency. Got a man down.
腹部中枪
GSW to the abdomen.
派辆救护车来爱迪生街1152号
Roll an ambo to 1152 Edison Street.
凯利
Kelly...
你是警察
you're a cop?
是的
Yeah.
斯科蒂
Scotty...
斯科蒂  你还跟布斯一起干吗
Scotty, are you working with Booth?
他死了
He's gone.
凯利
"Kelly"?
你怎么认识这家伙的
How do you know this guy?
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第十八集
你认识其中一名死者吗
You knew one of the victims?
是的  斯科蒂·詹森
Yeah. Scott Jansen.
他在一个叫罗恩·布斯的毒贩
He was part of a meth distribution crew
手下干活
run by a guy named Ron Booth.
好吧
Okay...
我三年前在布斯的团伙里卧底
I was under in Booth's crew three years ago.
因贩毒抓了他
Busted him for distro.
你觉得背后主使是布斯吗
Do you think Booth's behind this?
有可能
It's possible.
他两个月前刚出狱
He just got out of prison two months ago.
因为表现好提前假释  简直可笑
Early parole for good behavior. It's a joke.
你一直在关注他吗
So you keep tabs on this guy?
算是吧
Sort of.
只能说我不是很喜欢他
Let's just say I'm not a big fan.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
好了  三名白人过来
All right. Three white males approach.
近距离枪战  加西亚中枪
Close-quarter shootout. Garcia gets hit,
但他也开了几枪
but he gets a few shots off.
翻译     小酸奶   风城章鱼X   不高兴童鞋
击中了斯科蒂·詹森
Hits my boy Scott Jansen.
然后一号袭击者驾驶货车离开
And then Offender One leaves in the van.
翻译     小萝莉   Lynn_宁   H小欠   圈圈
二号袭击者驾驶轿车离开
Offender Two leaves in the sedan.
-丢下詹森等死  -没错
- And they leave Jansen to die. - Right.
这两个袭击者你认识吗
Do you recognize Offender One or Two?
校对     圈圈
不  我从来没见过他们
No, I've never seen them before.
他们不是以前布斯的人
They weren't part of Booth's old crew.
没有面部录像
We didn't get any hits on facial rec.
车辆信息有发现吗
Anything on the vehicles?
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
轿车没有牌照
The sedan had no plates.
货车有牌照  但是注册在
Van had tags, but it was registered
得州一个假地址名下
to a bogus address in Texas,
后期     8T
所以我已经对同款车发出通缉了
so I got a BOLO out on make and model.
好了  我们现在知道有人
All right, we got a rip crew
知道有货车要运冰毒
who knew about a van with liquid meth,
总监     圈圈
他们知道交易的时间和地点
and they knew when and where the deal was going down.
我觉得是布斯  他喜欢抢别人东西
My money's on Booth. He likes doing rips.
"免费的货最金贵"
"Better margins when the product's free."
他以前常常这么说
He used to say that all the time.
那好  试试看吧
All right, give it a shot.
但是不要惊动他
But let's not spook this guy.
你们跟媒体说这就是一起路怒凶杀案
You tell the press the homicide was a road rage incident.
-好的  -马上派人去盯着布斯
- Copy that. - Get eyes on Booth right away.
左边的就是布斯
That's Booth on the left.
好  好的
Yeah...okay.
好的  多谢
Okay, thanks.
-刚才是阿特沃特  -是吗  他查到什么
- That was Atwater. - Oh, yeah? What's he got?
他查了死者的一次性手机
He ran the DOA's burner phone.
他给布斯的工作号打了15通电话
He made 15 calls to Booth's work phone
就在过去这三天
over the last three days.
你们看见门上的摄像头了吗
You guys see the camera above the door?
看到了
Yeah.
你觉得他在里面制毒吗
You think he's cooking in there?
他不会这么蠢
He's smarter than that.
不管怎么说  我们得有人在里面盯着
Well, either way, we gotta get eyes inside.
让我去怎么样
How about mine?
你想重启你以前的卧底身份
You wanna dust off your old cover?
这是查案的最好办法  警长
Best way to chase this, Sarge.
那好  你作过证吗
Okay. You never testified?
没有  我们的证据足够
No, we had enough to prosecute
不需要我暴露我的卧底身份
without me needing to blow my cover.
而你确定这个凯利
And you're sure this Kelly character
在布斯的世界里活得好好的
is alive and well in Booth's universe?
至少就布斯所知  凯利目睹他
As far as Booth knows, Kelly got scared
被警察逮捕  吓坏了就回爱荷华老家了
when the cops busted him and scurried back home to Iowa.
那这个加瑞特·汤普森呢
What about this Garrett Thompson?
从罗斯蒙特出来的你的老搭档
Copper out of Rosemont you were partnered with.
-他怎么了  -这上面说
- What about him? - It says here
你的卧底身份是他的女友
you were under as his girlfriend.
是
Correct.
他在那次行动中被杀了
He got killed during that operation.
资料中有条附注说
There's a note in the GPR that says
有传闻说加瑞特反水了
rumors were going around that Garrett flipped
而且搬到墨西哥去了
and he moved to Mexico?
他是个好警察  布斯杀了他
He was good police. Booth murdered him.
怎么回事
What happened?
一直没找到他的遗体  所以我们没法立案
They never found his body, so we couldn't make a case,
但肯定是布斯
but it was Booth.
他一直不喜欢加瑞特
He never liked Garrett,
然后有一天  加瑞特就消失了
then one day, Garrett was gone.
一旦布斯把液体冰毒制作成结晶
Look, once Booth turns the liquid meth into crystal,
他就会有一大批货需要转移
he's gonna have a lot of product to move.
如果我卧底进去  介绍杰作为潜在买家
If I get in, I pitch Jay as a potential buyer,
就能一抓一个准
and we bust his ass.
那好  就这么办  不过听好
All right, let's do it. But listen.
我希望你去卧底是为了抓这个毒贩
I want you going under to bust a drug dealer,
而不是为了加瑞特的死报仇
not get revenge for Garrett's murder.
-明白  -很好
- Understood. - Good.
那好  去准备房子吧
All right. Get apartments set up.
东西你都有吧
You still backstopped?
驾照  亲属照片  应有尽有
Driver's license, family photos, you name it.
凯利随时可以行动
Kelly's good to go.
很好
All right.
你看看这个
Do you see this?
凯利以前是个毒虫  她只租得起这种
Kelly's a former tweaker. It's all she can afford.
两个字  外卖
Two words: takeout.
这是加瑞特吗
Is that Garrett?
是
Yeah.
你们俩看起来挺登对的
You guys look like a real couple.
演戏而已  你知道是怎么回事
All for show. You know the drill.
那好  你打算怎么跟布斯联系上
All right, so how are you gonna come at Booth?
斯科蒂·詹森的葬礼就在明天
Scotty Jansen's funeral is tomorrow.
布斯肯定会去
Booth'll be there.
主啊  愿他能获得永恒的安息
Eternal rest grant to him, O Lord,
让光明永远指引着他
and let light perpetual shine upon him.
W1S6315
William, one, Sam, six, three, one, five.
好  查到了一个
Okay, I got a hit.
车主是一位泰勒·威特洛克  19岁
Car belongs to Tyler Whitlock, 19.
进过两次少管所  最近因为非法持枪被抓
Two stints in juvie, recent bust for possession,
而且他是布斯的侄子
and he's Booth's nephew.
家族事业  多稀奇呢
Family business. How quaint.
愿他在主的恩典中  永享安宁
Through the mercy of God, rest in peace.
"沐浴主的恩典吧
"Rest in the Lord.
"愿主的智慧  决断和理性
"Let your intellect, your judgment, your reason...
"愿全知全能的主手中所有的美好
"In God personal and possessed of every perfection,
"都庇佑着你
"Almighty and all-knowing.
"沐浴主的恩典吧
"Rest in the Lord
"当他在福音中显身
"As He reveals Himself in the Gospel,
"便无上仁慈和光荣
"Merciful and gracious.
"要信主是好的
"Faith in God is good,
但更要信他  信我们的主更好"
but faith in Him as our own God is better."
阿门
Amen.
凯利
Kelly.
看来墓地还真是有鬼
Cemeteries really are haunted.
我不是鬼  罗尼
I'm no ghost, Ronnie.
我从没想过还能再见到你
I never thought I'd see you again.
我之前看新闻的时候看到了斯科蒂的照片
I was watching the news. Saw Scotty's picture come up.
可惜啊
It's a shame.
他们说是路怒症
They said it was road rage?
嗯  至少警察是这么说的
Yeah, that's what the cops say, anyway.
他是个好人  我很喜欢他
He was a good guy. I really liked him.
所以就来悼念他一下
Thought I'd pay my respects.
你现在住在这里
You living here now?
嗯  我刚搬回来
Yeah, uh...I just moved back.
我回家待了一段时间
I...I went back home for a little while.
俄亥俄吗
Ohio?
是爱荷华
Iowa.
我回去的时候正好...
I went back there right around the time...
我被关进监狱了
...I got locked up.
我当时有点紧张  就离开了
I got nervous, so...I left.
祝贺你出狱
I'm glad you're out.
我知道现在说这没什么意义了  不过...
And look, I know it doesn't mean much now, but...
新年派对上发生的事情我很抱歉
I feel bad about what happened at that New Year's party.
这种事也没办法
Things happen.
那个时候咱们几个都挺叛逆的
We were all a little crazy back then.
既然你现在回来了  打算干什么
So what are you up to now that you're back?
-重拾旧业  -搞涂料生意
- Back in business? - Paint business.
好吧
Okay.
我有个爱荷华的朋友来了这里
Listen, I have a friend that's in from Iowa.
-他在那边做买卖  -你是聋了吗
- He's a dealer out there-- - Hey, are you deaf?
我说了我在搞涂料生意
I'm in the paint business.
好  我明白了
Okay. Got it.
很高兴再次见到你  罗尼
It's good to see you again, Ronnie.
布斯那边还是没进展
Still no luck with Booth.
海莉以为他上钩了  可到现在还是没消息
Hailey thought that he bit, but so far, radio silence.
毒品抢劫事件也没有进展
We got nothing on the drug rip, either.
道上也没听到什么消息
There's no chatter on the streets.
缉毒组和反黑组那边也没有消息
No intel from Narcotics or Gangs.
你们应该庆幸我在这里工作
You guys are lucky I work here.
-你查到什么了吗  -嗯
- You got something? - Yeah.
我觉得佩雷斯好像参与了毒品抢劫
I think my unwitting, Perez, was in on the rip.
-什么意思  -我在系统里查了他的车辆行踪
- What do you mean? - I ran his vehicle through NVLS.
发现他的车上周曾三次停在
Turns out, his car was parked outside Booth's paint warehouse
布斯的涂料仓库外
three different times in the last week.
我猜他们肯定不是在讨论调色
Pretty sure they weren't talking about color palettes.
你觉得是佩雷斯和布斯一起策划的这起抢劫
So you think Perez and Booth planned the rip together?
他认识很多毒贩子  绝对是布斯的好搭档
He knows lots of dealers. Be a perfect partner for Booth.
也就是说布斯偷走材料  制毒
So Booth steals the product, cooks it,
让佩雷斯去卖
hands it over to Perez to sell?
这可真是天作之合啊
I mean, that's a match made in heaven.
没错  可问题是
Yeah, but the problem is,
如果佩雷斯是分销商  我们就没法搞了
if Perez is the distributor, we got no angle to play.
海莉向他们推荐杰这个买家也根本没用
Hailey pitching Jay as a buyer doesn't mean anything.
我们得去找找这个佩雷斯
We gotta do something about Perez.
你好啊  伙计  还好吧
'Sup, primo? You okay?
还在帮我们查我们毒品的下落吧
Still trying to figure out what happened to our product, man.
策划了这起抢劫的人必须要付出代价
Whoever did that rip has to pay.
这事儿可没这么搞的
We don't do business like that.
所以你不知道有谁参与其中
So you got no idea who was involved?
不知道
No, none.
那就好  我听说
That's good, because I hear
墨西哥那堆人已经开始悬赏拿人了
those boys from México got a bounty out.
一个人五万
50K a head.
-你确定  -确定
- ¿Estás seguro? - Seguro.
我还听说那起抢劫
And also heard that the rip--
趴下  趴下
Get down, get down!
-你受伤了吗  -没有
- You hit? - No!
这是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
我觉得应该是贩毒集团
I think that was the cartel, man.
那可是全自动步枪
Dude was rocking a full auto.
-你确定吗  -确定
- Are you sure? - Positive.
他们是冲你来的
They gunning for you?
-你参与抢劫了  -嗯
- You in on the rip? - Yeah, man.
我一直想自立门户
I've been trying to do my own thing.
你是疯了吗
You crazy?
那群墨西哥人会把你吊到桥下的
Them Mexican boys gonna hang your ass from a bridge.
我知道我知道
I know, I know!
你有地方去吗
You got some place to go?
我妹妹住在费城
My sister's place in Philly.
好  如果我是你  现在就收拾行李
All right, if I was you, I'd start packing now.
在我告诉你没事之前千万不要回来
And don't come back till I tell you it's cool.
-快去  -好
- Go. - Yeah, man.
嗨  亲爱的
Hey, honey.
那些是空包弹吧
Those were blanks, right?
是啊  佩雷斯怎么样
Hell yeah. How's Perez?
-他在换短裤  -他信了吗
- He's changing his shorts. - He bought it?
看起来是那样
It looks that way.
我沿路返回他那儿确定一下
I'll double back by his place to make sure.
好  注意安全
Cool. Be safe.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in here?
我给你的房东塞了20美元
I slipped a Jackson to your landlord.
告诉他我是你哥哥
Told him I was your brother.
他真的说我们很像
He actually said we look alike.
有钱能使鬼推磨
People do anything for money.
这可不酷  罗尼
That's not cool, Ronnie.
打包得不多啊
Packing light.
是啊  当你重头来过的时候没多少要打包的
Yeah, not a lot to pack when you're starting over.
很体贴啊
Oh, that's thoughtful.
给我带了杯咖啡
Brought me a coffee.
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
拜托  凯利  我开玩笑的
Come on, Kelly. I'm just playing.
你把我想成什么疯子了
What kind of a maniac you think I am?
还和加瑞特有联系吗
You still in touch with Garrett?
不  有阵子没联系了
No, I haven't talked to him in a while.
他是个好人
He was a good guy.
-他是个骗子  -是吗
- He was a liar. - Really?
是的  上一分钟他还在说戒指尺寸
Yeah, one minute he's talking ring sizes,
下一分钟就走了
and the next, he's gone,
所以  去他的吧
so...screw him.
那你干嘛还留着照片
So why keep the picture?
提醒自己不要再犯这种错
To remind me to never make the same mistake again.
你为什么搬回芝加哥
Why'd you move back to Chicago?
-你要干什么  -我就是好奇
- What are you doing? - I'm just curious.
我丢了工作
I lost my job.
-所以现在你破产了  -你怎么猜到的
- So now you're broke. - How'd you guess?
我准备回归了
Look, I'm ready to get back in the game.
我们可以互相搭把手
We could help each other out, you and me.
我不知道
I don't know.
你有些问题
There's something about you.
我可没那么神秘
I'm not that mysterious, man.
只是为自己着想
Just looking out for number one.
不在意别人
No one else is.
咱们从小的干起吧
Let's start small.
拿个包裹  我会短信告诉你地点
Pick up a package. I'll text you where it's at.
带到我办公室
Bring it to my office,
我们再聊其他的
then we'll talk about other things.
-像见我朋友那样  -对
- Like meeting my friend? - Yeah.
就像那样
Like that.
好
Okay.
久违了  凯利
It's good to see you again, Kelly.
精准邮递
她要去哪儿
Where's she going?
我觉得她有眉目了
I think she's got heat.
跟踪守则一  泰  别看着对方
First rule of tailing, Ty. Don't be seen.
他让我跟踪你的  好吗
He told me to follow you, okay?
不敢相信你又给他跑腿了
Can't believe you're working for him again, man.
我以为你会去大学打棒球
I thought you were going to college to play baseball.
是啊  可惜没成
Yeah, well, it didn't really work out.
我高三时被踢出来了  因为...
I got booted my senior year of high school 'cause...
他们在我储物柜发现了毒品
they found crank in my locker.
现在你给罗尼大叔推销产品
Now you're pushing product for Uncle Ronnie.
不能那么说  凯利
Ah...can't talk about that, Kelly.
不管是不是大叔  都是他让我那么做的
Uncle or no uncle, he'll put one in my ear.
-你知道他的风格  -是啊
- You know how he is. - Yeah.
没想到还会见到你
I didn't think I'd ever see you again...
特别是那晚之后
especially after that night.
-记得吗  新年前夜  -太久以前的事了
- You know, New Year's Eve? - That was a long time ago.
我得把这个带给罗尼
I gotta get this back to Ronnie.
要我送你吗
Do you want a ride,
还是想让我假装没认出你
or do you want me to pretend I never made you?
你能不能假装
Could you just pretend
-没见到我  拜托了  -好
- like you never saw me, please? - Yeah.
谢了
Thank you.
碘片
Iodine crystals?
加瑞特把你教的很好
Garrett taught you well.
真的只是食品添加剂
It's really just a food supplement.
完全合法
Purely legal.
所以你在测试不同的混合物
So you're testing different mixes.
有关油漆的  对
Of paint, yeah.
你没必要跟我兜圈子
You don't have to be coy with me.
只在必要的时候才跟你说
Just want you on a need-to-know.
好吧
Okay.
但我把你的包裹送来了
But I picked up your package...
现在你得和我朋友见面
so now you need to meet with my connect.
你怎么认识他的
How do you know this guy?
高中同学
We went to high school together.
没前科  很聪明
No priors. Smart.
如我所说  他很有钱
Like I said, he's got money to burn
在爱荷华州有很多买家
and lots of buyers in Iowa.
所以他和你一起上的高中
So he went to high school with you.
-塔夫脱  -飞鹰
- Taft. - The Eagles.
你知道我高中的吉祥物
You know my high school mascot?
-我真是受宠若惊啊  -我什么都记得...
- I'm flattered. - I remember everything...
甚至连你父母的名字都记得
even your parents' names.
艾米丽和罗伯特
Emily and Robert.
那是他们的名字  对吗
That's their names, right?
当我想起父母的时候
You know... when I think about parents,
我就会想起你和我讲你父亲
I think about that time you told me about your father,
讲他以前是怎么用旧钓鱼竿打你
and how he used to beat you with an old fishing rod.
我一定是喝醉了
I must've been drunk.
不  你说的是真的
No, you were just being real.
给我的人打电话  他叫瑞恩
Call my guy. His name is Ryan.
我会考虑的
I'll think about it.
好吧
Okay.
我说的对吗
So, was I right?
艾米丽和罗伯特
Emily and Robert?
不是  是乔安和理查德
No. Joanne and Richard.
杰夫·拉弗蒂
Jeff Rafferty?
你一定是霍斯特德
You must be Halstead.
谢谢你能在这么短的时间赶来见我
Thanks for meeting me on such short notice.
十队的墨菲让我给你带好
Murphy from the tenth says hi.
有什么能帮到你的吗
What can I do for you?
据我所知  你...
All right, so as I know, you, uh...
你是海莉那个
you were Hailey's case officer
罗纳德·布斯调查案的案件承办人
on the Ronald Booth investigation.
是你负责她的卧底工作吗
You handled her UC work?
-你看了文件  -是的
- You read the file. - I did.
你最近和她聊过吗
You speak to her recently?
我在布斯被提前释放之后就联系她了
I reached out after Booth got an early release.
-那感觉很糟吧  -糟都说的轻了
- That was probably upsetting. - Yeah, to say the least.
我们都需要发泄一下
We both needed to vent.
之后海莉说她又做回卧底了
Then Hailey said she was back under,
所以我就跟进了
so I checked in.
墨菲怎么样
How's Murphy doing?
他告诉过你
He ever tell you about the time
他嘉奖过一匹马吗
that he gave a citation to a horse?
-在芝加哥美食节那个周末  -别这么做
- Taste of Chicago weekend. - Please don't do that.
你不告诉我发生了什么  我是不会走的
I'm not going anywhere unless you tell me what's going on.
别管了  孩子
Let it go, son.
她是我的搭档  所以如果你知道
She's my partner, so if you know something
会置她于危险之中的什么的话  我需要知道
that's putting her in danger, then I need to know.
现在就要
Now.
我尽快赶来了
Hey. I got here as fast as I could.
出什么事了  你没事吧
What's the emergency? You okay?
这个
This.
12月31日发生的事
Time-stamped December 31st.
新年前夕
New Year's Eve.
发生什么了
What the hell happened?
海莉
Hailey.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我们得谈谈这件事
We gotta talk about this.
你背着我联系了拉弗蒂
You called Rafferty behind my back.
我没有别的选择
You know you didn't really give me a choice.
我知道你恨布斯
Look, I get that you-- you hate Booth
你想收拾他  但这  这太危险了
and you want to nail his ass, but...this...is too dangerous.
-这只是工作的一部分  -把一切都告诉我
- It's part of the job! - Just tell me everything.
我想帮忙  好吗  我保证
I wanna help, okay? I promise.
布斯刚从圣路易斯回来
Booth just got back from Saint Louis.
他在和一个联邦探员想要辨认的
He was there talking to a major player
主要人物说话
the feds were trying to ID.
所以在新年前夕...
So, New Year's Eve...
有个派对
there was a party.
我看到他落单了  他喝多了
I got him alone. He was drunk.
我以为我能把名字套出来  他在想着别的事情
I thought I could get a name. He had other things in mind.
套出来了吗
Did he?
没有
No.
我逃走了  加瑞特带我去了医院
I got away. Garrett got me to the hospital.
-你得告诉博伊特  -我能搞定的  杰
- You gotta tell Voight. - I can handle this, Jay.
这和我跟你说的话一样
That's exactly what I said to you.
你记得吗  然后你让我停下来
You remember that? And then you called me out
你说我满口胡言
and you told me I was full of crap.
让我在布斯的办公室放个摄像头
Let me put the camera in Booth's office,
从那里开始接手就好了
and we'll take it from there.
我没事的
I'm fine.
好吗  我保证
Okay? Promise.
你们能听到我说话吗
Can you guys hear me?
听得很清楚
Loud and clear.
泰  老大在吗
Hey, Ty. Big man in there?
-他今天的工作结束了  -真的吗
- He's done for the day. - Oh, really?
我还以为他在这
I thought he'd be here.
还想和他谈点事情
I wanted to talk to him about something.
他里面有卫生间  是吗
Hey, he's got a bathroom in there, right?
有  但他对外人比较敏感
Yeah, but he's a little crazy about guests.
-我很快出来  -这样不好吧  凯利
- I'll be two seconds. - Ah, I don't know, Kelly.
这个是钥匙吗
Is that the key there?
谢谢你  哥们
Thanks, buddy.
无视频内容
-有画面吗  -没有
- You got picture? - Negative.
海莉  布斯回来了  你得赶紧走
Hailey, Booth's coming back! You gotta get out of there.
别生我的气
Don't be mad at me, please,
凯利来了
but, uh...Kelly showed up.
她说她要用一下厕所
She said she needed to use the bathroom.
她现在在里面
She's in there right now.
好的  她搞定了  能看见了
All right, she did it. I got visual.
海莉  他来了  你赶紧走
Hailey, he's approaching. You gotta move.
出去
Get out.
你来了啊
There you are.
你在这里面干什么
The hell are you doing in here?
我来看你啊
I came to see you.
我  对不起  我刚才急着用厕所
I--sorry, I just had to use the bathroom.
我不在时谁都不能进来
No one comes in here without me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我以为没关系的
I didn't think it'd be a big deal.
给
Here.
你动过我的桌子吗
You touch my desk?
没有
No.
你没骗我  对吧
You're not lying to me, are you?
没有
No.
监狱让你变得多疑了
Prison made you paranoid, man.
监狱...让我更小心了
Prison...made me careful.
-我们得过去  -等等
- We gotta go. - Wait.
-杰  我们得  -先等等  等等
- Jay, we gotta-- - Just wait! Wait.
我刚坐完三年牢
I just did three years
因为有人跟警察告密
because someone talked to a cop.
我从来没跟警察告密
I never talked to the cops--
闭嘴  闭嘴
Shut up. Shut up.
我喜欢你
Now, I like you.
我在里面时还想着你
I thought about you when I was on the inside,
我想跟你做朋友
and I want us to be friends.
但如果你骗我
But if you lie to me...
我就杀了你
I'll kill you.
喂
Hello?
我找凯利
Uh, I'm looking for Kelly?
凯利现在不方便说话
Kelly can't talk right now.
你是谁
Who is this?
凯利的朋友罗恩
Kelly's friend Ron.
罗恩  我是瑞安
Ron? It's Ryan, man.
她跟你提过我  对吗
She told you about me, right?
是的
She did.
你给我五分钟就够了
Look, man, you just gotta give me five minutes.
你不会后悔的
You won't regret it.
我会跟她说你打电话给她了
I'll tell her you called.
是瑞安吗
Was that Ryan?
我跟你说过  他没问题
I told you. He's legit.
安排吧
Set it up.
我们是高中时认识的  锡达拉皮兹
We met in high school. Uh, Cedar Rapids.
-塔夫特高中  -什么之家...
- Taft High School. - Home of the...
-真的假的  -他不是闹着玩的
- Seriously? - He does not play.
雄鹰  雄鹰之家
Eagles. Home of the Eagles.
-好的  走吧  -好的
- Okay, let's go. - All right.
我们进去吧  就我跟他
Let's go inside. Just me and him.
确定吗  我很乐意...
Are you sure? I'm happy to--
就我跟他
Just me and him.
没关系  没什么好担心的
It's all good. Nothing to worry about.
走吧
Let's go.
-继续  -下面是什么
- Go ahead. - What the hell's down there?
-能安静说话的地方  -我在这里说就行
- A quiet place to talk. - I'm good talking right here.
不行  我们要下去  走吧
No, we're going down there. Come on.
去吧  坐下
Go ahead. Sit down.
把你的钱包给我
Give me your wallet.
瑞安·斯潘塞  你生日是什么时候
Ryan Spencer. When's your birthday?
六月八号
June 8th.
-你什么座  -什么座
- What's your sign? - My sign?
星座
Zodiac.
双子座  你什么座
Gemini. What's yours?
跟我说说锡达拉皮兹
Tell me about Cedar Rapids.
那里很冷  很平坦
It's cold and flat,
有很多可怜的种田小子想爽一把
and there's a lot of miserable farm boys looking to get high.
你跟凯利是在餐厅认识的
You met Kelly in some restaurant?
她是服务员  你是调酒师吗
She was a waitress, you were a bartender?
不是
No.
我们在高中认识的  塔夫特
We met in high school. Taft.
对
That's right.
塔夫特十字军
The Taft High Crusaders.
雄鹰
Eagles.
不过以前是十字军  很久以前
But it used to be the Crusaders, way back,
然后有人觉得不好
and then somebody got nervous
应该是96年的时候  换成了雄鹰
and I think they changed it to Eagles in, like...'96?
最后一个问题
One last question.
你睡了凯利多少次
How many times you screw Kelly?
-什么  -回答问题
- Excuse me? - Answer the question.
听着  等你准备谈正事的时候
Look, man, when you're ready to talk paper and product,
-再给我打电话  -多少次
- give me a call. - How many times?
放开我
Get your hand off me.
一次没有
None.
买卖做不成了  走吧
Deal's off. Take a walk.
我觉得他喜欢她
I think he's got a thing for her.
好像很痴迷  他问我是不是睡了她
Like, he's obsessed. He asked me if I slept with her.
我们可以利用这点
We can use that to our advantage.
耍一下他  重回交易
Play him a little bit, get the deal back on track.
耍他  你在说什么
"Play him"? What are you talking about?
他现在根基不牢  他需要买家
He's vulnerable. He needs buyers.
-我们可以利用...  -不不
- We can exploit that- - No. No.
够了就是够了
Enough is enough.
我们知道他能做出什么事
We know what this guy is capable of.
凯利要回爱荷华了  就这样
Look, Kelly is moving back to Iowa, end of story.
老大  我觉得你应该再考虑一下  因为...
Boss, I think that you should reconsider, because--
海莉  结束了
Hailey! It's over.
今晚就关掉卧底公寓
Now shut down that UC apartment tonight.
霍斯特德来电
喂  是我
Hey. It's me.
你有厄普顿的消息吗  我找不到她了
You heard from Upton? I can't track her down.
我以为你们在一起关闭卧底公寓
I thought you were together, closing up the apartment.
计划是这样  不过...
Yeah, that's the plan, but, um...
我私下跟你说
between you and me,
我找不到她了  我有种不好的预感
I can't find her, and I got a bad feeling.
我觉得她要私自行动了
I think she's making an off-the-book move.
好  我定位她的手机
Okay, I'm gonna ping her phone.
马上给你打电话
I'll call you right back.
你就是不放弃  是吗
You don't give up, do you?
我跟瑞安聊过
I was just talking to Ryan,
他说你们要做笔买卖
and he said you guys were about to do a deal,
然后就有点疯狂了
and then you went a little crazy.
-我不信任他  -我信任他
- I don't trust him. - Well, I do.
拿我的命信任
With my life.
他绝对可靠
He's as solid as they come.
好丈夫  好父亲
Good husband. Good father.
-他结婚了  -是啊
- He's married? - Yeah.
大概结了有五年了吧
Has been for, I don't know, five years?
可能更久
Maybe more.
他老婆也不错  不知道他干这行
Sweet girl too. Has no idea he's in the game.
所以他才这样  为了让她幸福
That's why he does all of this--to keep her happy.
祝他好运
Yeah, good luck with that.
怎么  你不信爱情
What, you don't believe in romance?
我不信我无法控制的事
I don't believe in things I can't control.
好吧
Okay.
你不信他  我也不逼你了
You don't trust him. I'm done pushing.
等等
Hold on.
如果我为你这么做
If I do this for you...
或许我们可以...在一起
maybe we could, you know...connect.
好啊
That could be nice.
怎么了  凯利  害怕吗
What's wrong, Kelly? Scared?
不  我不怕你  罗尼
No, I'm not scared of you, Ronnie.
我破产了  需要付房租  所以
I'm just broke, and I need to pay rent, so...
生意第一  好吗
business first, okay?
他来干什么
What's he doing here?
给我一个不开枪的理由
Give me one reason I don't shoot.
一万个如何  都在我后备箱里
How about 25,000 reasons? They're all in my trunk.
凯利告诉我要来这里
Kelly told me she was coming down here
想办法重回交易
to get the deal back on track.
我就想亲自把好消息送来
I figured I'd show up, get the good news in person.
罗尼  把枪收起来
Ronnie, put the gun away.
就当是表示信任的订金吧
Just consider it a good-faith down payment.
好  我们做买卖
Okay. We're on.
五公斤
Five kilos.
明早我会打电话告诉凯利具体信息
I'll call Kelly with the details in the morning.
你搞什么
What the hell was that?
-你搞什么  -小声点
- What the hell was that? - Keep your voice down.
我都是为了重回交易
"That" was getting a deal back on track
把杀人犯关回监狱
and putting a murderer back in prison.
博伊特让你停止卧底
Voight told you to shut this down.
是  但我在做我的本职工作
Yeah, well, I'm doing my job.
博伊特不会有问题的
Voight shouldn't have a problem with that.
他会有  相信我
He will, trust me.
但先不管他  我就有问题
But forget about that. I have a problem with it.
如果我无法信任你  我就无法做好工作
If I can't trust you, I can't do my job.
你无法信任我  你开什么玩笑
You can't trust me? Are you kidding me?
海莉  你太感情用事了
Hailey, you are way too emotional!
-我没有  -你现在思维根本不清楚
- I'm not emotional! - You're not thinking straight!
-这里的重点不是我  -那是什么
- This isn't about me. - Then what is it?
我们真的很快就能拿下他了
We are really close to nailing him.
我们不能把戏演完吗  求你了
Can we just play it out? Please?
我必须这么做
I need this.
怎么了
What's up?
你让我们关闭卧底公寓
I know you told us to shut down the UC apartment.
但是...交易回来了
but, uh...the meet's back on.
布斯突然给我打了电话
Booth called me out of the blue.
-什么时候  -几个小时前
- When? - A couple hours ago.
-我很担心海莉  -我也是
- I'm worried about Hailey. - Yeah, me too.
布斯很危险
Booth's dangerous.
虽然海莉很厉害  这一点我很清楚
Hailey's solid, though. I'm sure of it.
那么
Well...
你真的确定吗...
I mean, if you're sure...
确定
I am.
-那就去做吧  -好的
- So let's do the deal. - All right.
海莉今天晚点要跟布斯碰头
Hailey's meeting with Booth later today.
她会给我打电话的  确定碰头时间
She's gonna call me, set up a meet time.
我们会带着钱去拿下那个混蛋
We'll show up with the cash, take the son of a bitch down.
真高兴  我们的生意做成了
Glad we're finally doing this.
都在这里了
It's all there.
拿过来吧
Yeah, bring it over.
今晚吃饭庆祝一下怎么样
How about dinner tonight? To celebrate.
好的
Sure.
蓝色皮卡朝你们那边去了
Blue pickup rolling your way.
好的  我们伺机行动
All right, we wait for a visual exchange
或者等霍斯特德的信号
or Halstead's signal.
12罐油漆  来拿吧
12 cans of paint. Dig in.
等一下
Hey, hold on a second.
交货前  我们还是先花点时间
Let's just take a moment before we proceed...
-检查一下吧  -检查什么
- check a few things. - Like what?
窃听器之类的
Like wires.
好了  老兄  你用不着那样检查
Come on, man. You don't gotta do it like that.
他有枪
He's got a gun!
-后退  老兄  -我没有枪
- Back up, man! - I don't have a gun.
-冷静  -后退
- Hey, calm down. - Back up!
-冷静点  -后退
- Take it easy, man. - Get back!
拿下他们
Take 'em.
-你没事吧  -没事  我很好  快追
- You good? - Yeah, I'm good. Go!
泰勒  放下枪  让我来帮你  老兄
Tyler, drop the gun. Let me get you some help, man.
我知道你是警察
I knew you were a cop.
我只是不想相信
I just didn't want to believe it!
相信吧
Believe it!
承认你杀了加瑞特
Admit you killed Garrett.
快承认
Admit it!
你永远找不到他
You'll never find him.
海莉
Hailey.
海莉  海莉
Hailey. Hailey.
海莉  如果你杀了他  他就赢了
Hailey, he wins if you do it.
你不能这样做
This is not how you beat this.
求你了  海莉  求你了
Please, Hailey. Please.
不能这样做
This is not the way.
你要相信我
You gotta trust me.
起来
Get up.
大家都在莫利酒吧找你
Everybody's asking for you at Molly's.
我现在真的不想社交
Yeah, I don't really feel like being social right now.
好吧  普拉特请客
Well, Platt offered to buy shots,
真是万年难得的事
which is a once-in-a-decade thing,
你要不要再考虑一下
if you wanna reconsider.
还是算了
I'm all right.
我只想一个人静静
I just kind of feel like being alone.
那是不可能的
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
抱歉
Sorry.
不给我倒一杯吗
Wanna pour me a drink?
你的头怎么样了
How's your head?
没事  有点疼
It's all right. A little sore.
结束了  海莉  你抓到他了
It's over, Hailey. You got him.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
只是没有我想得那么好
It just doesn't feel as good as I thought it would.
让人想起太多死去的人
Stirred up too many ghosts, you know?
加瑞特吗
Garrett?
没错
Yeah.
那晚是他把我从布斯手上救下来
He was the one that pulled Booth off me that night.
阻止他...
He stopped him from...
强奸我...杀我
raping me... killing me.
很遗憾  你失去了他
I'm sorry you lost him.
听起来他是个不错的家伙
He sounded like a great guy.
没错  他是
Yeah, he was.
你爱他吗
You loved him?
总之...谢谢你来看我
Anyway, uh... thanks for coming by,
但老实说  我没事
but honestly, I'm fine.